A Guide to the Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Collection, 1856-2019
Shenandoah County Library
Shenandoah County Library
Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Collection, 1856-2019
Shenandoah County Library, location
2020-0001
29 boxes, 2 Oversize Folders, 1 Framed Item
Items retained by Mt. Zion Lutheran Church located in the Fairview Community west of Woodstock Virginia.
Administrative Information
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open to researchers without restrictions. Researchers must register and agree to all copyright laws and archives policies before using the collection. Please contact the Shenandoah County Library before visiting to use this collection.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donation with special restrictions
Rights Statement for Archival Description
...
Administrative Information
Mt. Zion Lutheran Church dates to 1829 when Abraham Smutz and his family sold land to a group of church trustees. This land contained a house that the deed required to be used as a school and church for any denomination. Mt. Zion’s Lutheran congregation met there twice a month during the 1870s.
In 1884 the Lutherans in the area began work on their own church building beside the Union church. The area surrounding the new church had previously been dedicated as a cemetery and the first burials at the site occurred in 1882.
In 1895 Mt. Zion Lutheran Church joined with St. Luke Lutheran Church to form a new parish. The coordination would last, with a few interruptions, to this day. In 1898 the two congregations joined with Lebanon Lutheran Church in the north end of the county to form an expanded parish. Since transportation was primitive the minister’s time at each church was limited. Mt. Zion hosted the minister on the 1st, 3rd, and 5th Sundays.
In 1908 a narthex and belfry was added to the church. The membership of the church numbered 156 adults in 1912. Other changes occurred over the next several decades as modern utilities came to the area. In 1925 electricity was added to the church’s parsonage. During the next decade a sink and water pump were also added. Finally, the church’s first bathroom with indoor plumbing was installed in 1943.
In 1948 when the church replaced the dual entrances and aisles, originally designed to segregate men and women, with a single entrance. During the project the church also added a large altar picture featuring Jesus in the Garden of Gethsemane to honor members who had fought in World War II. When these changes were dedicated in 1949, the church listed 150 communing members. The final major renovation to the church occurred in 1980-1981 when a social hall and parking lot was added.
In the decades that followed, the make-up of the Lutheran Parish to which Mt. Zion belonged changed drastically. Lebanon Church left the parish in 1969 when the other churches voted to realign the parish to include only two churches. This parish alignment would last until 1988, when Mt. Zion decided to become a one-church parish. However, the church was unable to support a minister on its own. In Mt. Zion and St. Luke rejoined in 2015 and continue to operate as a dual parish today.
Scope and Content
The Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Collections consists of approximately 35 linear feet of material stored in 29 boxes, 2 oversize folders, and 1 framed item. The materials contained within include documents, newspapers, ledgers, roster books, minute books, notebooks, scrap books, photographs, negatives, and bound publications. The collection is organized into the following 10 series:
Series I, Church Reports and Directories, 1958-2011 contains published church reports and membership directories
Series II, Church Services and Devotionals, 1935-2006 contains church bulletins, pamphlets from services, and various church devotionals
Series III, Newsletters and Newspapers, 1940-2019 contains various newsletters and newspapers published by the church or by other organizations that contain information about the church.
Series IV, Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council and Parish Council Minutes, 1900-2005 contains the minutes of the Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council and of the various Lutheran Parishes with which the church was affiliated.
Series V, Church Membership Records, 1956-2005 contains records related to the membership of Mt. Zion Lutheran Church including transfers, rosters, child rosters, and membership cards.
Series VI, Church Records, 1884-2013 contains various legal records and financial records and other documents produced by the church or related to its operations.
Series VII, Women of the Church, 1925-2013 contains the records of the Women of the Church group which was called at various times the Mt. Zion Ladies Aid Association, Mt. Zion Unitech Lutheran Church Women, Mt. Zion Church Women, and Mt. Zion Women of the ELCA.
Series VIII, Church Youth Contains Sunday School records, Cradle Roll records, and records from other youth groups and activities, including the Mt. Zion Luther League.
Series IX, Church Books, 1856-2009 contains various published and unpublished books and bound items related to the church including hymnals, music books, bibles, religious texts, ledgers and synod assembly minutes.
Series X: Audio Visual Materials, 1884-2007 contains photographs, audio recordings, and video recordings produced by the church.
Arrangement
All items are organized by material type within the following series:
Series I: Church Reports and Directories, 1958-2011
Box 1: 38758101567070 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Series II: Church Services and Devotionals
Box 2: 38758101567088 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Series III: Newsletters and Newspapers, 1940-2019
Box 3: 38758101567096 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Box 29: 38758101567369 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Series IV: Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council and Parish Council Minutes, 1900-2005
Box 4: 38758101567104 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Box 5: 38758101567112 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Box 6: 38758101567120 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Box 7: 38758101567138 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Box 8: 38758101567146 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Box 21: 38758101567310 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Series V: Church Membership Records, 1956-2005
Box 9: 38758101567153 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Box 10: 38758101567161 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Box 11: 38758101567179 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Series VI: Church Records, 1884-2013
Box 12 38758101567187 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Box 13 38758101567195 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Box 29: 38758101567369 Stack 10, Shelf 3
OVERSIZE FOLDER 1: 38758101567591 Map Case Drawer E, Folder 11
OVERSIZE FOLDER 2: 38758101567583 Map Case Drawer E, Folder 12
Series VII: Women of the Church, 1925-2013
Box 14: 38758101567203 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Box 15: 38758101567211 Stack 10, Shelf 2
Series VIII: Church Youth, 1919-2013
Box 16: 38758101567229 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Box 17: 38758101567237 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Box 18: 38758101567245 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Box 19: 38758101567252 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Box 20: 38758101567260 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Box 29: 38758101567369 Stack 10, Shelf 3
FRAMED STORAGE 38758101567575
Series X: Church Books, 1856-2009
Box 22: 38758101567286 Stack 10, Shelf 2
Box 23: 38758101567294 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Box 24: 38758101567302 Stack 10, Shelf 2
Series X: Audio Visual Materials, 1884-2007
Box 25: 38758101567328 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Box 26: 38758101567336 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Box 27: 38758101567344 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Box 28: 38758101567351 Stack 10, Shelf 3
Within each series, materials are organized chronologically with undated materials in the rear. The exception is Series X, Church Books which is sorted by size due to storage concerns.
An index for the recording in series X: Audio Visual Materials is:
Mt. Zion 01 Mt. Zion Remembers April 22 2010
Mt. Zion 02 Mt. Zion Remembers Oral History November 2009
Mt. Zion 03 Mt. Zion Reformation Video, October 29 1995
Mt. Zion 04 Easter Program at Mt. Zion 1992
Mt. Zion 05 Mt. Zion Lutheran Church 1996
Mt. Zion 06 Mt. Zion Church Homecoming September 1, 1996
Mt. Zion 07 Pastor Murray Christmas
Mt. Zion 08 Mt. Zion Church
Mt. Zion 09 Interview Mary Wetzel (93 years old) by Pastor Murray
Mt. Zion 10 Mt. Zion Youth Favorites
Mt. Zion 11 Baptism & Dave Program
Mt. Zion 12 Vacation Bible School, July 26-29 2004
Contents List
- Series I: Church Reports and Directories
  - 38758101567070 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 1)
    - Annual Reports (1 of 3), 1958-1976 (Box-folder 1.1)
    - Annual Reports (2 of 3), 1958-1976 (Box-folder 1.2)
    - Annual Reports (3 of 3), 1958-1976 (Box-folder 1.3)
    - Mt. Zion Church Directory, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 1.4)
    - Church Directories, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 1.5)
    - Parish Directories and Reports, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 1.6)
    - Mt. View Lutheran Parish Directory, 1970 (Box-folder 1.7)
    - Mt. View Lutheran Parish Directory, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 1.8)
    - Annual Reports, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 1.9)
    - Mt. View Lutheran Parish Directory, 1972 (Box-folder 1.10)
    - Mt. View Lutheran Parish Directory, 1973 (Box-folder 1.11)
    - Annual Report, 1975 (Box-folder 1.12)
    - Mt. View Parish Directory, 1977 (Box-folder 1.13)
    - Mt. View Lutheran Parish Reports, 1977 (Box-folder 1.14)
    - "From the Pastor" Annual Report, 1978 (Box-folder 1.15)
    - Annual Report, 1979 (Box-folder 1.16)
    - Annual Reports and Meetings, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 1.17)
    - Mt. View Lutheran Parish Annual Reports, 1981 (Box-folder 1.18)
    - Annual Reports, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 1.19)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Directory, 1984 (Box-folder 1.20)
    - Mt. Zion Annual Reports, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 1.21)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Directory, 1991 (Box-folder 1.22)
    - Mt. Zion Annual Reports, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 1.23)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Annual Reports, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 1.24)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Directory, 1997 (Box-folder 1.25)
    - Annual Report of the Congregation, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 1.26)
    - Annual Report of the Congregation, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 1.27)
    - “Annual Synod Report, Forms A & C,”2000 (Box-folder 1.28)
    - Annual Report of the Congregation, 2001 (Box-folder 1.29)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Annual Reports, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 1.30)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Directory, 2003 (Box-folder 1.31)
    - Annual Report of the Congregation, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 1.32)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Collection, 2011 (Box-folder 1.33)
- Series II: Church Services and Devotionals
  - 38758101567088 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 2)
    - “Does the World Ow Me a Living?” Lutheran Layman’s Movement for Stewardship Pamphlet, 1935 (Box-folder 2.1)
    - “Special Services Bulletins" (1 of 3), 1943-1995 (Box-folder 2.2)
    - “Special Services Bulletins" (2 of 3), 1943-1995 (Box-folder 2.3)
    - “Special Services Bulletins" (3 of 3), 1943-1995 (Box-folder 2.4)
    - “The Rededication of Mt. Zion Lutheran Church,” May 29 1949 (Box-folder 2.5)
    - Excerpts from Church Bulletins, 1964-2003 (Box-folder 2.6)
    - “Did You Know?” Excerpts from Church Bulletins, 1965-1977 (Box-folder 2.7)
    - Statistics from Church Bulletins, 1967-2005 (Box-folder 2.8)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Groundbreaking Service, June 29 1980 (Box-folder 2.9)
    - Church Bulletins (1 of 2), 1980 (Box-folder 2.10)
    - Church Bulletins (2 of 2), 1980 (Box-folder 2.11)
    - “Laying of the Cornerstone,” April 12 1981 (Box-folder 2.12)
    - Mt. Zion Dedication, May 3 1981 (Box-folder 2.13)
    - Church Bulletins (1 of 3), 1981 (Box-folder 2.14)
    - Church Bulletins (2 of 3), 1981 (Box-folder 2.15)
    - Church Bulletins (3 of 3), 1981 (Box-folder 2.16)
    - Church Bulletins, 1982 (Box-folder 2.17)
    - Church Bulletins, 1983 (Box-folder 2.18)
    - Advent Devotions, Mt. View Parish, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 2.19)
    - Church Bulletins, 1984 (Box-folder 2.20)
    - Church Bulletins, 1985 (Box-folder 2.21)
    - Church Bulletins, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 2.22)
    - Church Bulletins, 1988 (Box-folder 2.23)
    - Church Bulletins, 1989 (Box-folder 2.24)
    - “Because He Gave…” 1992 Lenten Devotional Booklet (Box-folder 2.25)
    - Church Bulletins, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 2.26)
    - Celebration of Marriage, Jason R. Roberts and Tracy L. White, April 24 1999 (Box-folder 2.27)
    - Church Bulletins, 1995 (Box-folder 2.28)
    - Announcements, July 28 1996 (Box-folder 2.29)
    - Church Bulletins, 1996 (Box-folder 2.30)
    - Church Bulletins, 1997 (Box-folder 2.31)
    - Funeral of Edith Hyde Lucas, November 5 1998 (Box-folder 2.32)
    - Church Bulletins (1 of 2) (Box-folder 2.33)
    - Church Bulletins (2 of 2) (Box-folder 2.34)
    - “Celebration of Holy Community and Installation,” Rev. Scott Maxwell, October 3 1999 (Box-folder 2.35)
    - Announcements, December 12 1999 (Box-folder 2.36)
    - Church Bulletins, 1999 (Box-folder 2.37)
    - Church Bulletins, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 2.38)
    - “A Celebration of God’s Grace,” Marriage of Candace Little and Scott Maxwell, April 27 2001 (Box-folder 2.39)
    - “The Celebration of Holy Communion and Ordination of a Pastor,” June 8 2002 (Box-folder 2.40)
    - Church Bulletins, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 2.41)
    - Church Bulletins, 2006 (Box-folder 2.42)
    - “Jacob and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat” Pamphlet, undated (Box-folder 2.43)
- Series III Newsletters and Newspapers
  - 38758101567096 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 3)
    - “Newspaper Clippings,” ca. 1940-2002 (Box-folder 3.1)
    - Church Clippings and Ephemera, ca. 1960-2002 (Box-folder 3.2)
    - Sallie Wetsel Gochenour Newspapers Clippings, ca. 1970 (Box-folder 3.3)
    - “The Lamplighter” Woodstock Area Lutheran Ministry Newsletter, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 3.4)
    - “The Mt. View Lamplighter,” Parish Newsletter, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 3.5)
    - “The Lamplighter” Woodstock Area Lutheran Ministry Newsletter, January-July 1972 (Box-folder 3.6)
    - “The Lamplighter” Mt. View Lutheran Parish Newsletter, August-December 1972 (Box-folder 3.7)
    - “The Lamplighter” Mt. View Lutheran Newsletter, 1973 (Box-folder 3.8)
    - “View Point” Church Newsletter (1 of 2), 1977-1979 (Box-folder 3.9)
    - “View Point” Church Newsletter (2 of 2), 1977-1979 (Box-folder 3.10)
    - “The Virginia Lutheran,” Jimmy Hepner, Mt. Zion Lutheran Article, July 1978 (Box-folder 3.11)
    - “The Outreach” Church Newsletter, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 3.12)
    - “The Outreach” Church Newsletter, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 3.13)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church 125th Anniversary Newspaper Clippings, 2009 (Box-folder 3.14)
    - “The Mountain Views,” Mt. View Parish Newsletter, 2015 (Box-folder 3.15)
    - “The Mountain Views” Mt. View Lutheran Parish Newsletter (1 of 2), 2016 (Box-folder 3.16)
    - “The Mountain Views” Mt. View Lutheran Parish Newsletter (2 of 2), 2016 (Box-folder 3.17)
    - “The Mountain Views” Mt. View Lutheran Parish Newsletter (1 of 2), 2017 (Box-folder 3.18)
    - “The Mountain Views” Mt. View Lutheran Parish Newsletter (2 of 2), 2017 (Box-folder 3.19)
    - “The Mountain Views” Mt. View Lutheran Parish Newsletter (1 of 2), 2018 (Box-folder 3.20)
    - “The Mountain Views” Mt. View Lutheran Parish Newsletter (2 of 2), 2018 (Box-folder 3.21)
    - “The Mountain Views” Mt. View Lutheran Parish Newsletter, 2019 (Box-folder 3.22)
    - Pastor Murray A. Ziegenfuss Article, undated (Box-folder 3.23)
  - 38758101567369 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 29)
    - Area Lutheran Evangelism Mission Newspaper Advertisement, Area Lutheran Ministers, April 15 1967 (Box-folder 29.7)
- Series IV: Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council and Parish Council Minutes
  - 38758101567104 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 4)
    - Mt. Zion and St. Luke Church Joint Council Minutes, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 4.1)
    - Church Council Minutes (1 of 7), 1971-1974 (Box-folder 4.2)
    - Church Council Minutes (2 of 7), 1971-1974 (Box-folder 4.3)
    - Church Council Minutes (3 of 7), 1971-1974 (Box-folder 4.4)
    - Church Council Minutes (4 of 7), 1971-1974 (Box-folder 4.5)
    - Church Council Minutes (5 of 7), 1971-1974 (Box-folder 4.6)
    - Church Council Minutes (6 of 7), 1971-1974 (Box-folder 4.7)
    - Church Council Minutes (7 of 7), 1971-1974 (Box-folder 4.8)
    - Church Council Minutes, October-November 1973 (Box-folder 4.9)
    - Church Council Minutes (1 of 6), 1975-1979 (Box-folder 4.10)
    - Church Council Minutes (2 of 6), 1975-1979 (Box-folder 4.11)
    - Church Council Minutes (3 of 6), 1975-1979 (Box-folder 4.12)
    - Church Council Minutes (4 of 6), 1975-1979 (Box-folder 4.13)
    - Church Council Minutes (5 of 6), 1975-1979 (Box-folder 4.14)
    - Church Council Minutes (6 of 6), 1975-1979 (Box-folder 4.15)
    - Church Council Minutes (1 of 8), 1977-1982 (Box-folder 4.16)
    - Church Council Minutes (2 of 8), 1977-1982 (Box-folder 4.17)
    - Church Council Minutes (3 of 8), 1977-1982 (Box-folder 4.18)
    - Church Council Minutes (4 of 8), 1977-1982 (Box-folder 4.19)
    - Church Council Minutes (5 of 8), 1977-1982 (Box-folder 4.20)
    - Church Council Minutes (6 of 8), 1977-1982 (Box-folder 4.21)
    - Church Council Minutes (7 of 8), 1977-1982 (Box-folder 4.22)
    - Church Council Minutes (8 of 8), 1977-1982 (Box-folder 4.23)
    - “Personal Appointment Book of B.B. Bly,” 1978 (Box-folder 4.24)
  - 38758101567112 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 5)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Meeting Minutes (1 of 7), 1982-1986 (Box-folder 5.1)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Meeting Minutes (2 of 7), 1982-1986 (Box-folder 5.2)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Meeting Minutes (3 of 7), 1982-1986 (Box-folder 5.3)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Meeting Minutes (4 of 7), 1982-1986 (Box-folder 5.4)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Meeting Minutes (5 of 7), 1982-1986 (Box-folder 5.5)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Meeting Minutes (6 of 7), 1982-1986 (Box-folder 5.6)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Meeting Minutes (7 of 7), 1982-1986 (Box-folder 5.7)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes, July 27 1986 (Box-folder 5.8)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (1 of 8), 1987-1989 (Box-folder 5.9)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (2 of 8), 1987-1989 (Box-folder 5.10)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (3 of 8), 1987-1989 (Box-folder 5.11)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (4 of 8), 1987-1989 (Box-folder 5.12)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (5 of 8), 1987-1989 (Box-folder 5.13)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (6 of 8), 1987-1989 (Box-folder 5.14)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (7 of 8), 1987-1989 (Box-folder 5.15)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (8 of 8), 1987-1989 (Box-folder 5.16)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (1 of 6), 1989-1991 (Box-folder 5.17)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (2 of 6), 1989-1991 (Box-folder 5.18)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (3 of 6), 1989-1991 (Box-folder 5.19)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (4 of 6), 1989-1991 (Box-folder 5.20)
  - 38758101567120 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 6)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (5 of 6), 1989-1991 (Box-folder 6.1)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (6 of 6), 1989-1991 (Box-folder 6.2)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (1 of 3), 1992 (Box-folder 6.3)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (2 of 3), 1992 (Box-folder 6.4)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (3 of 3), 1992 (Box-folder 6.5)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (1 of 4), 1994 (Box-folder 6.6)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (2 of 4), 1994 (Box-folder 6.7)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (3 of 4), 1994 (Box-folder 6.8)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (4 of 4), 1994 (Box-folder 6.9)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (1 of 3), 1995 (Box-folder 6.10)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (2 of 3), 1995 (Box-folder 6.11)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (3 of 3), 1995 (Box-folder 6.12)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (1 of 3), 1996 (Box-folder 6.13)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (2 of 3), 1996 (Box-folder 6.14)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (3 of 3), 1996 (Box-folder 6.15)
    - Church Council Minutes (1 of 4), 1997 (Box-folder 6.16)
    - Church Council Minutes (2 of 4), 1997 (Box-folder 6.17)
    - Church Council Minutes (3 of 4), 1997 (Box-folder 6.18)
    - Church Council Minutes (4 of 4), 1997 (Box-folder 6.19)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Minutes (1 of 6), 1998-1999 (Box-folder 6.20)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Minutes (2 of 6), 1998-1999 (Box-folder 6.21)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Minutes (3 of 6), 1998-1999 (Box-folder 6.22)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Minutes (4 of 6), 1998-1999 (Box-folder 6.23)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Minutes (5 of 6), 1998-1999 (Box-folder 6.24)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Minutes (6 of 6), 1998-1999 (Box-folder 6.25)
  - 38758101567138 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 7)
    - Church Council Minutes (1 of 8), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 7.1)
    - Church Council Minutes (2 of 8), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 7.2)
    - Church Council Minutes (3 of 8), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 7.3)
    - Church Council Minutes (4 of 8), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 7.4)
    - Church Council Minutes (5 of 8), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 7.5)
    - Church Council Minutes (6 of 8), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 7.6)
    - Church Council Minutes (7 of 8), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 7.7)
    - Church Council Minutes (8 of 8), 2000-2001 (Box-folder 7.8)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Minutes (1 of 5), 2002 (Box-folder 7.9)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Minutes (2 of 5), 2002 (Box-folder 7.10)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Minutes (3 of 5), 2002 (Box-folder 7.11)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Minutes (4 of 5), 2002 (Box-folder 7.12)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Minutes (5 of 5), 2002 (Box-folder 7.13)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Minutes (1 of 5), 2003 (Box-folder 7.14)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Minutes (2 of 5), 2003 (Box-folder 7.15)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Minutes (3 of 5), 2003 (Box-folder 7.16)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Minutes (4 of 5), 2003 (Box-folder 7.17)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Minutes (5 of 5), 2003 (Box-folder 7.18)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (1 of 5), 2004 (Box-folder 7.19)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (2 of 5), 2004 (Box-folder 7.20)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (3 of 5), 2004 (Box-folder 7.21)
  - 38758101567146 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 8)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (4 of 5), 2004 (Box-folder 8.1)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (5 of 5), 2004 (Box-folder 8.2)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (1 of 6), 2005 (Box-folder 8.3)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (2 of 6), 2005 (Box-folder 8.4)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (3 of 6), 2005 (Box-folder 8.5)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (4 of 6), 2005 (Box-folder 8.6)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (5 of 6), 2005 (Box-folder 8.7)
    - Church Council Meeting Minutes (6 of 6), 2005 (Box-folder 8.8)
  - 38758101567310 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 21)
    - Shenandoah Lutheran Parish Joint Council Minutes and Record including Marriages, 1900-1944
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Minute and Church Record Book, 1912-1943
    - Shenandoah Lutheran Parish Join Council Minutes, July 1961-July 1968
    - Shenandoah Lutheran Parish, Mt. Zion Lutheran Congregation, Church Council Minutes, 1958-1966
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Council Minutes, 1967-1970
- Series V: Church Membership Records, 1956-2005
  - 38758101567153 Stack 10, Shelf 3 (Box 9)
    - “Pastor Sheetz Transfers,” 1956 (Box-folder 9.1)
    - “Pastor Eggen Transfers” (1 of 2), 1958-1962 (Box-folder 9.2)
    - “Pastor Eggen Transfers” (2 of 2), 1958-1962 (Box-folder 9.3)
    - “Pastor Fuller Transfers,” 1964-1966 (Box-folder 9.4)
    - Child Roster Mt. Zion Lutheran Church, 1965-2000 (Box-folder 9.5)
    - Membership Questionnaire (1 of 2),ca. 1970 (Box-folder 9.6)
    - Membership Questionnaire (2 of 2),ca. 1970 (Box-folder 9.7)
    - Baptisms, Transfers, and Deaths, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 9.8)
    - Parish Attendance and Offering, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 9.9)
    - Mt. Zion Lutheran Church Membership Lists, 1973 (Box-folder 9.10)
    - Pastor Arehart Transfers, 1973 (Box-folder 9.11)